What's up good people? It's Amanda Seals back to spread some more joy and celebrate another one of
the amazingly talented young folks featured in this year's AT&T Rising Future Makers Showcase.
Now see, this program is all about honoring 25 rising star HBCU students, teaming them up with
today's makers, mavens, and mobiles, and giving them valuable tools and connections to take their
dreams to new heights. Let's shine a spotlight on the incredible Jameer Stanford Hargraves,
a junior business management major in Washington, D.C. Not only is Jameer a first-generation
college student, but he's also the first in his family to graduate high school. I see you, Jameer.
Now back home in Delaware, Jameer helped raise $3 million to build a safe haven for teenagers,
a project that will impact the lives of nearly 50,000 young people. The organization also helps
other first-generation HBCU students to turn their dreams into reality. One of the greatest
privileges in my life has come from working with educators who care deeply about making
knowledge accessible to young minds. Jameer, you're doing just that at such a young age,
forming meaningful connections and being a role model and mentor. It's truly amazing.
Jameer, your shining spirit and determination are lighting the path for others to follow.
So keep being a brilliant star that you are. Now visit the AT&T Dream in Black microsite to learn
about the entire AT&T Rising Future Makers Showcase Class of 2023. Congrats again. I can't wait to see
what y'all do.